{
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "1",
      "back": "一"
    },
    {
      "front": "2",
      "back": "二"
    },
    {
      "front": "3",
      "back": "三"
    },
    {
      "front": "4",
      "back": "四"
    },
    {
      "front": "5",
      "back": "五"
    },
    {
      "front": "6",
      "back": "六"
    },
    {
      "front": "7",
      "back": "七"
    },
    {
      "front": "8",
      "back": "八"
    },
    {
      "front": "9",
      "back": "九"
    },
    {
      "front": "10",
      "back": "十"
    },
    {
      "front": "maintenant",
      "back": "今"
    },
    {
      "front": "personne",
      "back": "人"
    },
    {
      "front": "jour, journée",
      "back": "日"
    },
    {
      "front": "mois, lune",
      "back": "月"
    },
    {
      "front": "feu",
      "back": "火"
    },
    {
      "front": "eau",
      "back": "水"
    },
    {
      "front": "arbre, bois",
      "back": "木"
    },
    {
      "front": "or, argent, monnaie",
      "back": "金"
    },
    {
      "front": "terre, sol",
      "back": "土"
    },
    {
      "front": "origine, source, vrai, livre",
      "back": "本"
    }
  ]
}
